a place where there is If you're alive,
I'll protect you
It's okay,
let's go ahead and move on
The moon will always come to
the moon The wind will come
and see the light of the sky
He's back on his feet yet again!
He may fall... Luffy!
But he gets right back up every time!
Why can't you just stay down?
You'll kill yourself!
Luffy!
He's battered and bruised! Luffy!
He's tired and out of breath!
I'm here!
He's so good!
He's so with a glamour in his eye!
All for the sake of his friends!
Now this is a daily backbite!
I don't know what to say!
I'm so curious, I can't see straight!
Luffy!
We love you!
I'm gonna cry!
You will, Luffy!
You can do it!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
The crowd has spoken!
Sure has touched our hearts!
No one has ever lasted
this long against our boss!
No one has ever shown so much courage!
You idiots! Jeez!
Don't you realize you're
telling me of the enemy?
Come on, boss.
Boss!
Come on, boss! Come on, boss!
Just you wait.
I'll end this soon.
A zombie sword!
You have to do better than that!
Oh, no!
He can't dodge!
His poor legs are too worn out to run!
Here!
Let me put you to rest!
Slash the beam!
Boss goes on the offensive!
He slowed down the
cannonball, but to what end?
Flying Foxy Fighter!
Watch out for my flying fist!
They're gonna knock you out
at the speed of a cannonball!
He's using the Flying Foxy
Fighter to finish his foe!
It may be slow now, but once the
beam wears off, there's no escape.
Listen, he used this beam on you
a few seconds before the ball.
Dodge as soon as you're back to normal.
I can move.
Oh, Sean recovers, but is it too late?
Nice try, but I'm too fast.
Watch out!
That thing's about to blow!
Here you go.
A parting gift.
What do you like to that?
Oh, I don't think Straw Hat will
be getting up from that one.
Is he trying to kill him?
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
oh,
oh.
You're going down.
Is that so?
And how do you plan to beat me if
you can't even stand up straight?
But never mind.
If that's how you want it,
then others have to pound your face
in until you stay down for good.
Megaton, nine tails!
Come, come, come!
Rush!
That's it!
Such intensity!
The fighters are unleashing a flurry
of fists at lightning speed! Go!
Slaughter that box! So
fast! So strong! So brutal!
Wait, what?
He stopped moving!
Oi!
I think Strahd had his bait!
No wait!
He's on his knees, but he's still moving!
Unlike our boss who's standing,
but strangely frozen in place!
How did he...
Oh, no, boss!
It's a mirror!
A piece of mirror has
fallen from Shulha's hand!
It was stuck in my afro.
I got it when I broke the mirror.
Come on!
Oh,
oh, oh,
oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh.
Boss, no!
Eight seconds.
Could this be the end?
Seven seconds.
Till what?
Six?
Say it ain't so!
Five!
Hey, come on, you guys!
Don't just sit there!
Get along with me! Four!
All right, we'll all be to the end!
It's everyone together now!
Three, two, one!
He's flying!
Up goes our boss!
high into the sky!
And now he finally comes down!
Get dead! Get dead!
Outside the battlefield!
Ladies and gentlemen, the final round of
the daily back fight has come to an end!
After an epic battle between captains,
our boss's legendary record of 920
wins and zero losses has been broken!
I won't let you take a
single member of my crew,
even if it kills me!
Let's hear it for strong!
Help you!
Our boss truly lost.
We've seen it all today, folks.
Hey, don't just sit there, guys.
The boss needs our help.
Let's do something.
You can count me in.
Let's go.
It's the end of the day.
The boss needs me.
The Davey-backed giant has been toppled.
And the boy with the
tiny crew and the massive
afro has seized the
day in a grand fashion.
You little Chef, who do you think you are?
Take this, and this!
He's not that!
He's really hurt!
You poke him to death!
Yeah, afro power my butt.
It was a close call if I've ever seen one.
Whoa, hey, let's not
disrespect the afro here.
Look, he's waking up.
Where am I?
What happened? Is it over? Did I win?
That wasn't just a dream, was it? Was it?
You don't need to freak out.
You beat him.
What a relief.
Everyone else said you'd lose, but not me.
You're a bad liar.
Guess it would have been
a real pain if you'd lost.
Imagine being stuck in a boat with Foxy.
Screw that.
Boss wait you gotta take
it easy hey Rubber Boy
I was pretty attached to
that Windstreak of mine
I'm not pleased about you
ruining it boss no I'm
kidding brother let's
shake What a man the best!
You're too kind, boss!
Take my shoulder, throw them straight!
Oh, no!
This guy's a real piece of work.
You forget the rules already? Come on!
You got no crewmates to choose!
He's right!
We haven't made the final exchange yet!
Guess I'll take your flag!
You monster!
We'll strip my poor crew of their
livelihood without a second thought.
I don't need your sail.
You've got to use that
to go places, after all.
Do you hear that?
We're safe.
That's nice and all, but I'm
afraid it's not that easy.
We have a flag on our sail, too.
We don't need your pity.
You want fair and square, so take it.
I got a plan.
I don't actually have
to take the sail off the
boat as long as I can take
the mark off the sail.
And I can do that with paint.
Once you have a new flag,
you should be fine, right?
Thank you, Slot.
Your kindness is all.
It sucks.
Aw, you guys don't have to bow to me.
We're not.
Hey, rubber boy, I'll
make you pay for this.
Just wait.
That's supposed to be a joke, right?
I know what you're thinking, but I won't.
Ride on stilts ever again
we'll catch up to the
village too i don't care
how many years it takes.
Us you made
it back we
brought you a souvenir.
You're hurt are you all right?
Aw, this? It's nothing.
Thank you for your help.
Is that why you accepted the fight?
Because you wanted to help him?
And here I thought you were
just being stupid again.
Man, you're rude.
What? What's happening?
Guys, I don't like this.
I'm the champion.
You dig?
Great.
Another weirdo.
Champion of what? Obviously.
I'm the world champion of hole digging.
As crazy as it sounds, I'm
challenging my own record as we speak.
That's no excuse for wrecking
the old stilts guy's house.
Where is he supposed to live?
Huh?
What old stilts guy?
You can manage while I'm gone, right?
Uh-huh.
I'll wait as long as I have to.
But you better come back
a champion, okay, Grandpa?
You bet I will. Don't you worry.
I promise I'll make you proud.
It can't be.
It's really you?
Well, of course.
Grandpa!
I missed you so much.
I was so lonely without you.
You turned into a fine young man.
I'm so sorry I didn't
get to watch you grow up.
I didn't mean to worry you.
I hope you can forgive me.
I didn't see that one coming.
When I thought about how hard my
grandpa was working on his world record,
it inspired me to start
on a record of my own.
And suddenly, before I knew it,
all my loneliness turned into
a passion for hole digging.
Looks like it all worked out, huh? Yes.
I don't know how to thank you.
Farewell, my friends.
I won't forget you.
Again, thank you so much.
Take care on your way home, old man!
You too!
Wherever you may go, I
pray for your safe journey.
Yeah!
Just hold on, Mary.
We'll find a ship right
to fix you up in no time.
Yeah!